<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<LanguageData>
<PES_CaravanDismiss>{0} is no longer heading towards our colony and tracked by our reconnaissance system.</PES_CaravanDismiss>
<PES_PrisonerDead>{0} is getting really angry now because one of the prisoner they want is dead. They will now revenge on the colony.</PES_PrisonerDead>
<PES_AllSlaveDead>{0} changes their raiding goal to Extortion, because all the colonists they want to enslave are dead.</PES_AllSlaveDead>
<PES_CommunicationEstablished>We have established communication with {0}. Use Comms Console to contact them.</PES_CommunicationEstablished>

<PES_Detected_Title_Human>Crowd Incoming</PES_Detected_Title_Human>
<PES_Detected_Title_Animal>Herd Incoming</PES_Detected_Title_Animal>
<PES_Detected_Text_Human>The reconnaissance system in our colony has detected that an unknown human crowd is moving toward our colony. Their faction and intention are unknown. The reconnaissance system is trying to identify more information about it. Detail information is in the security report.</PES_Detected_Text_Human>
<PES_Detected_Text_Animal>The reconnaissance system in our colony detected that an unusual animal herd is moving toward our colony. The reconnaissance system is trying to identify more information about it. Detail information is in the security report.</PES_Detected_Text_Animal>

<PES_Hostile_Confirmed>Hostile Entity Confirmed</PES_Hostile_Confirmed>
<PES_Hostile_Text_Human>The reconnaissance system in our colony has confirmed the incoming human crowed is a hostile raiding team. More information is in the security report.</PES_Hostile_Text_Human>
<PES_Hostile_Text_Animal>The reconnaissance system in our colony has confirmed the incoming animal herd are mad animals. More information is in the security report.</PES_Hostile_Text_Animal>

<PES_Neutral_Message>The reconnaissance system in our colony has confirmed the incoming crowd is nonhostile. See more in security report.</PES_Neutral_Message>
<PES_Neutral_Message_Animal>The reconnaissance system in our colony has confirmed the incoming herd is nonhostile. See more in security report.</PES_Neutral_Message_Animal>

<PES_Caravan_Confirmed>"{0}" has entered the vision range of our colony, all information revealed. </PES_Caravan_Confirmed>

<PES_Update_NeedSkill>A colonist with at least Level {0} in construction is required to construct this upgrading</PES_Update_NeedSkill>

<PES_Spot_SkyFaller_Big>The reconnaissance system in our colony has spotted an anomalous large object in the sky</PES_Spot_SkyFaller_Big>
<PES_Spot_SkyFaller_Small>The reconnaissace system in our colony has spotted incoming drop pods</PES_Spot_SkyFaller_Small>

<PES_Warning_Meteorite>Warning: Meteorite Impact</PES_Warning_Meteorite>
<PES_Warning_Meteorite_Text>The reconnaissance system in our colony has confirmed that the incoming large object is a meteorite. The impact spot has been successfully calculated. See the security report for more information.</PES_Warning_Meteorite_Text>

<PES_Warning_ShipPart>Warning: Ship Part Impact</PES_Warning_ShipPart>
<PES_Warning_Shippart_Text>The reconnaissance system in our colony has confirmed that the incoming large object is a large piece of an ancient ship! The impact spot has been successfully calculated. See the security report for more information.</PES_Warning_Shippart_Text>

<PES_Warning_DropPodAssault>Warning: Drop Pod Assault</PES_Warning_DropPodAssault>
<PES_Warning_DropPodAssault_Text>The reconnaissance system inour colony has confirmed that the incoming drop pods are actually containing enemies! Their landing spot has been successfully calculated. See the security report of more information.</PES_Warning_DropPodAssault_Text>

<PES_Infestation_Letter>Unusual Deep-Ground Motion Detected</PES_Infestation_Letter>
<PES_Infestation_Text>The ground-penetrating scanner in the colony has detected an anomolous movement deep in the gound. It is clear that this is a sign for upcoming infestation.</PES_Infestation_Text>

<PES_Notify_ResoucePod>The incoming drop pods have been confirmed to be resource pods.</PES_Notify_ResoucePod>
<PES_Notify_RefugeePod>The incoming drop pods have been confirmed to be containing a refugee.</PES_Notify_RefugeePod>
<PES_Notify_ShipChunk>The incoming large object in the sky has been confirmed to be ship chunks.</PES_Notify_ShipChunk>

<PES_Warning_Flare_Early>Solar Flare(Early Stage)</PES_Warning_Flare_Early>
<PES_Warning_Flare_Early_Text>A solar flare is about to blast the planet. Radar and statellite uplink has already stop functioning because of the electromagnetic interference. Other electronic devices are predicted to stop working in about 12 hours when the solar flare finally hit this planet.</PES_Warning_Flare_Early_Text>
</LanguageData>

