<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <PES_TryToCallOnRadio>Try to call {0}</PES_TryToCallOnRadio>

  <PES_TryContactPrologue_Unknown>Since we have not established communication with "{0}", we can try to broadcast a message from this comms console, hoping they could receive this message and reply to us. But beware, we don't know they are our allies or enemies. \n\nSo, {1} decide to send a message saying that:</PES_TryContactPrologue_Unknown>

  <PES_TryContactPrologue_Neutral>Although the reconnaissance system in our colony has identified {0}} is friendly, we still cannot establish communication with them. We can broadcast a message, urging them to reply to us ASAP. \n\nSo, {1} decide to send a message saying that:</PES_TryContactPrologue_Neutral>

  <PES_TryContactPrologue_Hostile>Caution: {0} has been recognized by our reconnaissance system as an incoming menace, but we haven't uncovered all of their information. We can try to broadcast a message demanding them to state their intention. \n\nSo, {1} decide to send a message saying that:</PES_TryContactPrologue_Hostile>

  <PES_TryContactPrologue_Mechanoid>Initiate greeting protocol with those soulless machines\n</PES_TryContactPrologue_Mechanoid>

  <PES_TryContact_Persuasion_Unknown>"This is {0} from {1} speaking. Please state your intention of coming to our colony and confirm that you have no hostility towards us."\n</PES_TryContact_Persuasion_Unknown>
  <PES_TryContact_Persuasion_Neutral>"This is {0} from {1} speaking. We have confirmed that you are not hostile to our conoly. Please contact with us ASAP!"\n</PES_TryContact_Persuasion_Neutral>
  <PES_TryContact_Persuasion_Hostile>"This is {0} from {1} speaking. Our reconnaissance system has identified your hostile activity. NAME YOUR INTENTION! Repeat, NAME YOUR INTENTION!"\n</PES_TryContact_Persuasion_Hostile>

  <PES_TryContact_Intimidation_have_mortar>"Your location has been confirmed by us! State your intention immediately or be prepared to take a rain of our mortar fire!"\n</PES_TryContact_Intimidation_have_mortar>
  <PES_TryContact_Intimidation_no_mortar>"Your location has been confirmed by us! State your intention immediately or our commandos will launch an immediate assault!"\n</PES_TryContact_Intimidation_no_mortar>

  <PES_TryContact_Beguilement>"This is an SOS message from {0} of {1}: we are currently under heveay attack by mechanoids; countless centipedes, lancers and scythers are flocking into our base! We need immediate military assistance! Right Now! Ahhhhhhhhhh"\n</PES_TryContact_Beguilement>
  <PES_TryContact_Beguilement_FactionConfirmed>"This is {0} from {1} speaking. {1} is currently occupying {2}. Any incoming corps with unidentifiable intention would be recognized as a threat to {1}"\n</PES_TryContact_Beguilement_FactionConfirmed>
</LanguageData>